globalcraze.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which [Globalcraze.com](http://www.globalcraze.com/ "Globalcraze.com") collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [Globalcraze.com](http://www.globalcraze.com/ "Globalcraze.com"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and content offered by [Globalcraze.com](http://www.globalcraze.com/ "Globalcraze.com") .

## Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, Internet Protocol (IP), Date / Time stamp, Number of clicks to analyze Trends, Track user’s movement around the site, and gather Demographic Information. the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Web browser cookies

A “ _cookie_ ” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Globalcraze to recognize you each time you visit this site(customization etc.). Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

## How we use collected information

[Globalcraze.com](http://www.globalcraze.com/ "Globalcraze.com") may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

\- To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and contents.  
\- To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to send them information and updates pertaining to their order.

## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Our Site is in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

## Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "privacy policy").

## Compliance with children’s online privacy protection act

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

## Visitor Tracking / Statistical Analysis

Globalcraze makes use of analytical software such as _Google Analytics_ for statistical purposes. For the stat analysis purpose, your IP (Internet Protocol) address, browser, screen resolution, operating system are captured. We, at Globalcraze, use this information only for statistical purpose and do not share it with any third party.

## User Comments

Globalcraze allows users to comment on the site. However, we hold all rights to accept or reject any comments based on our discretion. While commenting on Globalcraze, please refrain from using content that is not suitable.

## Changes to this privacy policy

Globalcraze has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## [Contacting us](http://www.globalcraze.com/contact-us/ "Contacting us")

Feel free to contact the blog Author using the [contact page](http://www.globalcraze.com/contact-us/ "Contacting us") for any other query / information. 

The following two tabs change content below.

  * Bio
  * Latest Posts

[GlobalCraze](http://www.globalcraze.com/) is based on WordPress Blogging tips, SEO, Social Media, Technology even more by Chetan Gupta who covers useful articles for Newbie bloggers and readers. Chetan Gupta is a Passionate blogger by profession and resides in New Delhi, India. He is a WordPress and Internet enthusiast. Apart from blogging, he takes delight in listening music, surfing internet and he loves to playing chess. ;) [Chetan on Facebook](http://www.facebook.com/itschetanhere) and Follow him [on Twitter](http://www.twitter.com/GlobalCraze)
